<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content=""SafePulse Crime Prevention Area: Enhancing public safety through advanced monitoring and community engagement. Secure spaces, safer lives.""Community policing enhances public safety by fostering trust and collaboration between law enforcement and the community to solve local problems together.""Enhance public safety with advanced surveillance systems. Monitor, protect, and respond swiftly to ensure community security.""Neighborhood Watch Programs boost public safety by uniting communities to prevent crime and enhance vigilance through local cooperation.""Enhance public safety with crime analysis and mapping, leveraging data to identify patterns, prevent crime, and allocate resources effectively."Empower youth through engagement programs focused on public safety, fostering community involvement, and promoting a safer environment for all.Swift and efficient emergency response ensures public safety by providing immediate assistance during crises, minimizing harm, and safeguarding communities."Explore essential public safety services ensuring community protection, emergency response, and crime prevention for a safer environment.""Enhance public safety with disaster preparedness: essential tips and strategies for effective response and recovery in emergency situations.""First Responders Training enhances public safety by equipping professionals with essential skills to manage emergencies effectively and save lives."Effective crisis communication ensures public safety by delivering timely, clear information during emergencies to protect and inform the community."Emergency Medical Services (EMS): Rapid response and expert care for public safety, ensuring community health during emergencies. Vital lifeline in critical situations."Ensure public safety with effective traffic safety measures. Reduce accidents, enhance road security, and protect lives through vigilant traffic management and education."Enhancing public safety through innovative road design and engineering solutions. Promoting safer, more efficient transportation systems for all.""Promote public safety by preventing drunk driving: Educate, enforce laws, and encourage sober choices to save lives and reduce accidents on the road."Ensuring public safety through speed limit enforcement helps reduce accidents, save lives, and promote responsible driving in communities."Explore Pedestrian Safety Initiatives for enhanced Public Safety, focusing on innovative measures to protect and empower walkers in urban environments.""Explore Vehicle Safety Standards ensuring public safety by regulating design, construction, and performance to minimize accidents and injuries on the road.""Public Safety ensures community well-being by addressing health threats, preventing injuries, and promoting safe environments for all."Effective disease control and prevention ensures public safety by minimizing health risks, controlling outbreaks, and promoting community well-being."Vaccination programs enhance public safety by preventing disease outbreaks and protecting community health.""Learn essential quarantine procedures to ensure public safety during health crises, minimizing risks and protecting communities efficiently.""Promoting public safety through health education campaigns, ensuring communities stay informed and protected."Ensure public safety with effective water sanitation monitoring. Track and maintain clean water standards to protect community health."Ensure public safety with effective air quality control, monitoring pollutants to protect health and well-being in communities.""Must Read: Essential public safety tips and guidelines to keep you informed, prepared, and safe. Stay updated with crucial information for your well-being."Ensure public safety with essential fire safety tips: prevention, emergency response, and education. Protect lives and property by staying informed and prepared."Learn how fire codes and regulations ensure public safety by preventing hazards, protecting lives, and promoting safe building practices.""Ensure public safety with professional smoke detector installation. Protect lives and property with reliable, early fire detection systems.""Learn essential firefighting techniques to enhance public safety and effectively manage fire emergencies. Stay prepared and protect your community."Effective wildfire management strategies protect communities and ensure public safety by preventing, controlling, and mitigating wildfires. Stay informed, stay safe."Boost public safety with effective awareness campaigns. Educate, inform, and protect communities through targeted communication strategies."">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logo.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.tad2fb25f436bbf23bc39d2b27009ca53 a{
font-size:16px;
}
.vbba335ac83d6d0cf6f2ecf558d308e9f p,.vbba335ac83d6d0cf6f2ecf558d308e9f a,.vbba335ac83d6d0cf6f2ecf558d308e9f span,.vbba335ac83d6d0cf6f2ecf558d308e9f label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.c56178d80d80e04a436102a4520b8731b{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.4px;
padding-right:7.6px;
padding-top:4.8px;
padding-bottom:4.8px;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 14.8px 30.3px;
border-radius: 0;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
a:hover{
color:;background:!important;
}
.nav-link{
color: #823c3c;

}
.t09943426e9e956b2dc0819a3046a7338:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50.5px 50px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.vbba335ac83d6d0cf6f2ecf558d308e9f a,.tad2fb25f436bbf23bc39d2b27009ca53 a{
color:#101010!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 17.5px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
.tad2fb25f436bbf23bc39d2b27009ca53 p,.tad2fb25f436bbf23bc39d2b27009ca53 span,.tad2fb25f436bbf23bc39d2b27009ca53 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer{
background:#0b0b0b;
color:#ffffff;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/index.html"  ><img alt="img/logo.jpg" src="img/logo.jpg"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="collapse navbar-collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="d-flex ml-auto navbar-nav align-items-center"><li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/news.html"  >News</a></li>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270 dropdown-toggle nav-link" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">SafePulse Crime Prevention Area</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/index.html"  >SafePulse Crime Prevention Area</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/community-policing.html"  >Community Policing</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/surveillance-systems.html"  >Surveillance Systems</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/neighborhood-watch-programs.html"  >Neighborhood Watch Programs</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/crime-analysis-and-mapping.html"  >Crime Analysis and Mapping</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/youth-engagement-programs.html"  >Youth Engagement Programs</a>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270 nav-link dropdown-toggle" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/emergency-response.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Emergency Response</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/emergency-response.html"  >Emergency Response</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/services.html"  >Services</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/disaster-preparedness.html"  >Disaster Preparedness</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/first-responders-training.html"  >First Responders Training</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/crisis-communication.html"  >Crisis Communication</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/emergency-medical-services-ems.html"  >Emergency Medical Services EMS</a>
  
<li class="nav-item dropdown ">
<a class="wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270 dropdown-toggle nav-link" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/traffic-safety.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Traffic Safety</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/traffic-safety.html"  >Traffic Safety</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/road-design-and-engineering.html"  >Road Design and Engineering</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/drunk-driving-prevention.html"  >Drunk Driving Prevention</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/speed-limit-enforcement.html"  >Speed Limit Enforcement</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/pedestrian-safety-initiatives.html"  >Pedestrian Safety Initiatives</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/vehicle-safety-standards.html"  >Vehicle Safety Standards</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270 dropdown-toggle nav-link" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/public-health-safety.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Public Health & Safety</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/public-health-safety.html"  >Public Health & Safety</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/disease-control-prevention.html"  >Disease Control Prevention</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/vaccination-programs.html"  >Vaccination Programs</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/quarantine-procedures.html"  >Quarantine Procedures</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/health-education-campaigns.html"  >Health Education Campaigns</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/water-sanitation-monitoring.html"  >Water Sanitation Monitoring</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/air-quality-control.html"  >Air Quality Control</a>
  
<li class="nav-item  dropdown">
<a class="nav-link dropdown-toggle wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/must-read.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Must Read</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/must-read.html"  >Must Read</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/fire-safety.html"  >Fire Safety</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/fire-codes-and-regulations.html"  >Fire Codes and Regulations</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/smoke-detectors-installation.html"  >Smoke Detectors Installation</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/firefighting-techniques.html"  >Firefighting Techniques</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/wildfire-management.html"  >Wildfire Management</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/public-awareness-campaigns.html"  >Public Awareness Campaigns</a>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270" rel=nofollow href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li></ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for SafePulse</h1>
<p>At SafePulse one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by SafePulse and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: </p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in SafePulse. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, SafePulse, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>SafePulse follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of SafePulse.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on SafePulse, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that SafePulse has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>SafePulse's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>SafePulse does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
SafePulse</br>
994-945-9983</br>
8855  Ridge Road</br>
Lincoln, NE, 68508</br>
United States</br>
</br>
OliverCarterRoam3@gmail.com</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="container pt-5 py-4" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="wce91d37e4fc54929cf32fb1e659f7270" href="https://safetyblog.netlify.app/about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
<p><p>The content provided on this blog is for informational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. The information presented here is not meant to substitute professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health provider with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this blog.</p>

<p>The authors and administrators of this blog are not healthcare professionals, and viewing this content does not create a doctor-patient relationship. We do not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, relevance, or timeliness of any information on this site and are not responsible for any errors or omissions in this information nor for the availability of this information.</p></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
